Are you telling me to apologize?
（しずか）
わたくしに謝れっておっしゃるの？
Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!
お母さまにも謝れなんて
言われたことありませんわ
Are you telling me to apologize?
わたくしに謝れっておっしゃるの？
Not even my mother ever told me to apologize!
お母さまにも謝れなんて
言われたことありませんわ
Sakaki Shizuka
Newbie Voice Actress
Ah, wonderful!
ああ～ん いいですわ
もっと ああ～ん
More! Ah!
わたくしを ほめてほめて
天にも昇る気持ちにしてくださいな
Keep lifting me up to heaven with your sweet praises!
Just like that!
（しずか）ああ～ん いい～
（サラリーマン）うん？
Are you telling me to apologize?
わたくしに謝れとおっしゃるの？
お母さまにも…
Even my mother—
Miyamori Aoi
Production Assistant
（キーボードを打つ音）
（太郎(たろう)）はあ～
What's wrong?
（あおい）
どうしたんですか？
Takanashi Tarou
Production Assistant
Being considerate to people all the time sure wears you out.
（太郎）
いや～ もう気ぃ使いすぎて
疲れちゃったのよ
Maybe I'm just too nice of a guy.
俺ってさ つくづく
気遣いの鬼だよな～
I've seriously never met anyone whose self-image was as off as yours.
Yano Erika
Production Assistant
（矢野(やの)）
あんたほど他人の評価と
自分の評価が
ズレてるヤツは
いないよね
No easing up on the
tongue-lashings, huh, Yano-san?
相変わらず毒舌っすね
矢野さんは
はあ～ でもさ～
I guess we PAs are doomed to be the resident punching bags.
制作って しょせんサンドバッグに
なるしかないんだよな～
（太郎）あ？　おいおい宮森
（あおい）うん？
Oh, come on, Miyamori.
Hm?
At least gimme a "Sounds tough!" or something.
大変ですね～ くらいは言ってよ
Sounds tough.
大変ですね
Whatever. I'm more of a lone wolf anyway.
いいんだ いいんだ
どうせ俺なんて孤高の虎ですよ
Don't insult the poor wolves.
虎に謝れ
I Screwed Up Badly
Madoka Hironori
Episode Director
Why would you keep the AC on in this weather?
（円(まどか)）
だから なんで この季節に
クーラーつけてるんですか！
Because it's too damn hot!
Kinoshita Seiichi
Director
（木下(きのした)）
だから暑いんだよ！
What's going on?
どうしたんですか？
The director keeps turning on the AC!
いや 監督が消しても消しても
クーラーつけちゃって
This room gets hot so easily.
ここって熱こもんない？
No it doesn't.
いえ 別に
If you're cold, wear a couple more layers!
まあ寒かったら服 着れば
If you're hot, then take some off!
暑かったら
脱げばいいじゃないですか
I can't take any more off! I'd be buck naked!
これ以上 脱げねえよ
裸になっちゃうよ！
There's a zipper on your back.
背中にチャックついてますよ
No there's not!
（木下）ついてねえよ！
（円）太ってるから暑いんですよ
You feel hot because you're fat.
You don't have to be so mean about it.
かっ！　傷つくな～
その言い方
Besides, I've lost a whole kilo since I started on Exodus!
第一 俺「えくそだすっ！」に
入ってから１キロも痩せたんだよ！
A fat lot of good that does!
１キロじゃ分かりませんよ
And I can't do storyboards without a cool head!
（木下）
それにさ 頭冷やさないと
絵コンテが描けないんだもん！
You've gotta be kidding me!
（円）もんっじゃないっすよ
（あおい）はあ～
Oh, food's done!
ごはん温まった！
から揚げ から揚げ
Fried chicken! That's the stuff!
（円）…ったくも～う
（エアコンを切る音）
Gimme a break...
Ah, Oi-chan!
（絵麻(えま)）
あっ おいちゃん
Did Zuka-chan get in touch with you?
ずかちゃんから連絡あった？
Yasuhara Ema
Keyframe Animator
Oh, about what?
（あおい）
えっ 何？
She has an anime audition today!
今日アニメのオーディションだって
初めての
Her first one!
Audition? I didn't kno—
オーディション？
聞いてない！　あっ
Wait, is that what she called about?
（あおい）
もしかして…
あの電話！　あちゃ～
Shoot!
What's wrong?
何？
So she called you?
絵麻んとこ連絡あったんだ
We're meeting on Sunday, right?
あしたの日曜
集まることになってるでしょ？
I texted her about that earlier.
そのことで
さっきメールしたの
That's when she told me about the audition.
そしたら
これからオーディションだって
I see.
そっか
Then let's wish her luck!
じゃあ みんなで
受かるように祈ろう！
Fried chicken! Fried chicken!
（木下）
かっら揚げ かっら揚げ♪
Good afternoon.
（絵麻）
お疲れさまです
Fried chicken!
から揚げ～
Who turned the AC off?!
誰だよ クーラー切ったの！
Prussia
Studio
Let's do this.
よし！
10:00 ~ 23:00
TV Anime
"My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining
things (tentative)"
Audition
Next, please.
（岸谷）では 次の方
（しずか）ハッ
Mori Shinobu-san, you're up.
Kishitani Hiroshi
Sound Production
森(もり)しのぶさん お願いします
Right!
（森）
はい！
I'm Mori Shinobu from 24 Produce!
（森）
24(トゥエンティ－フォー)プロデュースの
森しのぶと申します
Thank you for this chance!
よろしくお願いしま～す
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart, but I
guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do
everything in my power. You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know
what am I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
Good afternoon!
（相馬(そうま)）
おはようございま～す
え！　相馬れなさん！
超売れっ子声優の？
Souma Rena-san? The famous voice actress?
I see you're quite busy these days.
いや～ 最近 忙しそうですね
You're working on ten shows right now, aren't you?
レギュラー10本
あるらしいじゃないですか
Not to mention the role in the
Fallen Robot: Sadoka Mazoka movie!
「背徳ロボ サドカマゾカ」の
劇場版も決まったんでしょ？
You get all the best ones!
持ってきますね～
Oh, stop it!
やめてくださいよ～
I've still got such a long way to go!
私なんか まだまだですから
（岸谷）
ま～た謙遜しちゃって～
You're always so humble.
Pros like her are auditioning for this too?
こんな すごい人も
オーディション受けるのか
I don't stand a chance.
これじゃあ受かるわけないよ
No, what am I saying? I practiced a lot!
いやいや そんなことない
あれだけ練習したんだ
I can do this!
やればできる私！
Okay, next!
（岸谷）
じゃあ次 坂木(さかき)しずかさん
Sakaki Shizuka-san!
はい！
Yes, sir!
I'm Sakaki Shizuka from Akaoni Productions!
赤鬼(あかおに)プロダクションの
坂木しずかと申します！
Thanks so much for having me!
よろしくお願いいたします！
Thanks for coming.
（若柱）
はい よろしく　落ち着いてね
Just relax.
ほえ～
よろしくお願いします
I really appreciate it.
We're finally halfway through!
（篠田）
やっと半分ですね
How many people did we call for this audition?
オーディション何人くらい
呼んだんでしたっけ？
Shinoda Toshiki
Director
Tsujita Mitsuyoshi
Line Producer
Nakayamata Nobukatsu
Maker Producer
Something like 120, right?
（中山田）
120人くらいですね
That was a bit overkill...
もうちょっと
絞ってもよかったんじゃ…
I won't be able to remember the first ones by the time we're done.
最初のほう
分かんなくなっちゃうんですよね～
Are you ready?
（若柱）
じゃあ いいかな 始めますよ
Let's start.
はい！
Okay!
I'm sure you know, as it's in the script,
（若柱）
資料に書いてあるから
分かると思うけど
but you're the big sister of the eleven-girl harem.
（若柱）
ハーレム11人衆の中の
お姉さんね
Make her sound a bit agitated.
ちょっと高ビーにお願いします
Say your name and the role when the recording light comes on.
キューランプ出したら
お名前と役名言って始めてください
はい！
Okay.
Wakabashira Hirokazu
Sound Director
始めて
Go ahead.
ハッ 西園寺(さいおんじ)レナ役を
受けさせていただきます
I'm Sakaki Shizuka from Akaoni Productions!
I'm auditioning for the role of Saionji Rena!
赤鬼プロダクションの
坂木しずかです
Thanks for hearing me!
よろしくお願いします
Are you telling me to apologize?
わ… わたくしに
謝れっておっしゃるの？
Even my mother has never once told me to apologize!
お母さまにも謝れなんて
言われたことありませんわ
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
Harem of eleven / Sister
Scene (1)
Onee-san can't contain her feelings, confused by her first, blooming love
Sister "Are you telling me to apologize? Even my mother has never once told
me to apologize!"
"Tell me what you want! Anything! I shall do everything in my power.
You have my word."
"This is the first time such an emotion took hold of me. I do not know what am
I supposed to do. My heart starts racing every time I set my eyes on you!"
"Ah, wonderful! Praise me, praise me more and make me feel like I'm in heaven!"
My harem might be falling apart,
but I guess I'm just imagining things (tentative)
Audition script
Harem of eleven / Sister (1 page blank)
Characters
I'm sorry...
すみません
Continue.
（若柱）
続けて
Tell me what you want! Anything!
なんでも私に話してくださいな
Her nerves are really getting to her.
随分 緊張してるな～
I shall do everything in my power. You have my word.
That's for sure.
（辻田）
ですね～
She sounds a bit amateurish, but I don't mind that.
でも こういうこなれてない感じ
嫌いじゃないですよ
This is the first time I've experienced such an emotion.
こんな気持ち初めて
わたくし どうしていいのか
分かりませんの
I haven't a clue about what to do!
あなたのことを考えるだけで
胸が締めつけられそうなんですの
My heart races whenever I lay eyes on you!
Ah, wonderful!
ああ～ん いいですわ
もっと 私を ほめてほめて
Yes, keep going and lift me up to heaven with your sweet praises!
天にも昇る気持ちに
してくださいにゃ
ハッ うっ… すみません
I'm sorry!
止めない！
Don't stop!
Ah, great!
ああ～ん いいですわ
もっと…
More! Ah!
ああ～ん 私を ほめて
天にも昇る気持ちにしてくださいな
Lift me up to heaven with your sweet praises!
24 Produce
Akaoni Production
Sadaoka Masumi
Haruyama Yuuki
Mori Shinobu
Sakaki Shizuka
Uechi Masami
Ikezaki Katsura
Icaros
Accel Two
Actors' Union
Fugen Pro
24 Produce
Akaoni Production
All set for the filming meeting on Monday?
（本田(ほんだ)）
月曜の撮影打ちは段取った？
Yes, I've reserved the meeting room for 16:00.
はい 16時に会議室
押さえてあります
I'm glad to see this episode's going much smoother than episode 4 did.
（本田）
さすがに４話と違って
今度はバタついてないみたいだね～
I learned a lot from that.
ちょっと経験値 上がったんで
I'm so jelly, Miyamori. You get tomorrow off?
いいな～ 宮森　あしたは休みか
（あおい）
はい
Yes.
I've gotta work.
俺 仕事なんだよな
一人で家いてもつまんねえだろ
It'll be boring being home alone,
so why not come here anyway?
会社 来たら？
I'm meeting with my high school friends tomorrow.
あしたは高校の時の
友達に会うんです
え！　かわいい子いる？
Any cuties?
They all are.
みんな かわいいですよ
マジマジ？
俺の将来の嫁いる？
For reals? Reckon one could be my wife one day?
いません！
No.
There's always a chance, right?
いるかもしれないだろ
どこで会うの？　何時から？　うっ
Where are you meeting? When—
Just ignore him. You're good to go.
もう こいつの相手
しなくていいから帰りな
Honda Yutaka
Production Manager
I'll be going, then! Bye!
お疲れさまでした
お先に失礼しま～す
See you!
（矢野）お疲れさま
（本田）お疲れ～
Bye!
Seaweed
Meal
Mom
Incoming Call
Hello?
は～い
You finally answered!
（あおいの母）
あ～ やっとつながった
I watched your Es Dookus!
（母）
見たよ 「えそくだすっ」
Exodus!
（あおい）
「えくそだすっ！」
Yeah, that.
I thought it didn't air back at home.
（あおい）
うちのほうじゃ やってないでしょ
Your dad had cable TV installed.
お父さん
ケーブルテレビ入ったから
We saw your name in the credits!
最後に
あおいの名前が出てきたよ
"Miyamori Aoi."
（母）
宮森あおいって
I kept watching that part over and over.
お母さん そこだけ何度も見た
Just that?
（あおい）
そこだけ～？
I see you're making the most of things.
あおい 頑張ってるんだな～って
But I didn't really get what the show was about.
（母）
でもね～
お話はよく分かんなかった
Your dad was really happy to see your name show up, too.
お父さんもね
あおいの名前 見て喜んでた
He told me to send you some rice.
（母）
お米でも送ってやれって
Just don't send too much.
（あおい）
少しでいいよ
Are you eating properly?
（母）
ちゃんと食べてる？
コンビニのお弁当ばかりじゃダメよ
You can't live off those convenience store meals.
I know.
I eat other stuff too!
（あおい）
あっ ばっかりじゃないから
I'll send you some cabbage again.
（母）
あ～ 白菜も また送るから
It's okay. I still have some.
まだ あるからいいよ
Will you be back for the new year?
お正月には帰ってくるの？
Yeah, but I don't know exactly which day yet.
（あおい）
うん？
何日になるか分かんないけど
Hold on, you should talk with Dad too.
（母）
あ～ ちょっと
お父さんと代わるから
Huh? It's okay!
（あおい）
えっ いいよ～
Dad! Dad!
（母）
お父さん お父さん
Nope, he's not waking up.
（母）ダメだ 起きない
（あおい）ハハハ
Your sister's out at a party with people from the credit union.
お姉ちゃんは今日
信金の飲み会があってね
I've gotta go now.
じゃあ そろそろ切るよ
Make sure to stay warm at night!
（母）
暖かくして寝なさいよ
You've always caught colds pretty easily.
あんた 昔から
おなか壊しやすいんだから
ふう… 分かった 分かった
じゃあね おやすみ
I know, I know.
Anyway, night!
Good night!
（母）
おやすみ
New message
Zuka-chan
Close
ふっ ハァ ふっ ハァ…
（携帯電話の着信音）
（しずか）ふっ！　うん？　ハァ
Oi-chan?
（しずか）おいちゃん？
（あおい）うん
What's up?
（しずか）
どうした？
Sorry I missed your call the other day.
Things got a bit hairy.
（あおい）
この間 ごめんね
電話くれたのにバタバタしてて
It was my bad for calling when you're so busy.
ううん こっちこそ
忙しい時にごめんね
I heard you had an audition today.
（あおい）
今日オーディション
だったんだよね？
Yeah.
Oh... You can tell us more about it tomorrow!
（あおい）
あっ じゃあ そんなこんな話も
またあした 聞かせてね
Yeah, we'll have plenty of time to talk.
うん 積もる話は
あした ゆっくり　うん じゃあね
Later!
Laters!
（あおい）
じゃあね
Kamiyama High School
Animation Club
The Divines:
Seven Lucky Warriors
Kamiyama High School
Animation Club
The Divines:
Seven Lucky Warriors
Kamiyama High School
Animation Club
The Divines:
Seven Lucky Warriors
Kamiyama High School
Animation Club
We, the seven lucky warriors,
will defeat all evil lurking in these lands!
（布袋）
ちまたにはびこる悪は
この七福神が成敗してやる！
You stand no chance!
（恵比寿）
覚悟しろ！
（ゼウス）
ハッハッハ～ お前らが
私に勝てるわけがあるまい
You will never beat me!
（毘沙門天）
そ… それはどうかな
We'll see about that!
Both the gods and the Buddhas are on our side!
（大黒天）
俺たちには
神も仏もついてるんだぜ
Don't underestimate us!
（弁財天）
ナメるんじゃないわ
（寿老人）
いくぞ ベイベー
Let's do this, baby!
We fight for justice!
（福禄寿）
正義のために戦うのじゃ
Time to roll! The Divines: Seven Lucky Warriors!
（布袋）
いくぞ！　神仏混淆(こんこう)！
（全員）
七福神！
Here, taste my spear!
おっ… 俺のヤリを
受けてみるんだな
Surrender to my beat!
私のビートにしびれなさい！
（全員）やあ！
（風の音）
The seven lucky warriors fight evil and bring peace and happiness to people everywhere.
（あおい）
悪と戦い 人々に
平和と福をもたらす七福神
Their fight will continue to rage on!
彼らの戦いは まだまだ続く
Thank you all for watching.
（あおい）
ご試聴ありがとうございました
The screening of The Divines:
Seven Lucky Warriors has ended.
これにて「神仏混淆七福陣！」の
上映を終わらせていただきます
Thank you!
ありがとうございました
（４人）
Where you want to go next?
（生徒１）
次どこ回る？
Let's try the crepes class 2-3 made!
（生徒２）
２年３組のクレープ屋
行ってみようよ
I heard they're pretty good.
（生徒３）
吹奏楽
講堂でやってるらしいよ
（生徒１）
じゃあ そっち先回ろっか
Toudou Misa
3D Artist
Zuka-chan-senpai!
（美沙(みさ)）
ずかちゃん先輩～
あっ みーちゃん
Mii-chan!
I knew you'd be here first!
やっぱ ずかちゃん先輩が
一番だった
You used to be first in the clubroom too.
いつも部室に来るのも
最初でしたもんね
You were all just late.
みんなが遅すぎるんだよ～
Zuka-chan, Misa! Were you waiting long?
（絵麻）
ずかちゃん 美沙
（絵麻）待った？
（美沙）きゃ～ 絵麻先輩
Ema-senpai!
You're already here!
先に来てたんだ
I had to buy a couple things.
うん 買い物
Zuka-chan, I haven't seen you since Golden Week.
ずかちゃん
ゴールデンウィーク以来だっけ？
Yeah. You've lost some weight!
うん　絵麻 痩せたね
Just wore myself a bit thin.
やつれただけだよ
Who's left?
これで あとは…
Imai Midori
University Student
Sorry, I overslept!
（みどり）
すいませ～ん
私が寝坊しちゃって
You haven't changed a bit, Rii-chan!
あっ やっぱ
りーちゃん変わってない
You're the youngest and all, but you're always so late!
一番後輩なのに
いつも遅れてたもんね
Sorry, it's just who I am.
すみません　ギリギリ体質で
Now then, shall we?
さて じゃあ行きますか
The Girl from the Town
of the Rainbow
Soon this town will be gone for good.
（少女）
もうすぐ この町は
全て消えてしまうの
What will happen to you then?
（少年）
そしたら きみはどうなるの？
I will be gone as well.
（少女）
私も 消えるの
Cinema
The Girl from the Town
of the Rainbow
All shall return to nothing.
That is the way of the world.
（老人）
全ては無に帰る
それが世のことわりじゃ
Not while I'm around!
（少年）僕がなんとかする！
（少女）えっ
Huh?
I don't want to let you or the Town of the Rainbow disappear!
（少年）
虹の町も きみも 消したくない！
The story was so great!
（みどり）
いや～ ストーリー
よかったですね
It was ninety minutes long...
（あおい）90分の劇場か～
（みどり）うん？
How many cuts would that be? Like twelve hundred?
何カットくらいあるんだろう？
1,200カットくらい？
I heard that the storyboards weren't done yet in May.
（絵麻）
５月にまだ絵コンテ
終わってないって聞いたけど
（みどり）
ほお
Despite that, the animation was really smooth.
（絵麻）
それにしては
作画安定してたね
All the effects were done with CG.
エフェクトは全部ＣＧだったね
They blended in really well.
（美沙）よくなじんでる
（みどり）あっ
I liked how the main girl played with her voice.
主役の子 声張るのうまかった
She really did justice to the role.
女優さんなのに すごく合ってたし
But I'd say the best was the uncle, played by Yotsugi-san.
一番うまかったのは
おじいさん役のよつぎさんかな
He usually does cool-guy roles,
so I didn't know he could nail this too!
カッコいいイメージあったけど
ああいう役もできるんだ
You all sound like industry professionals!
なんかみんな業界人っぽい
コメントっすね
Do we?
そう？
でっ この後どうする？
Anyway, what are we doing after this?
Going drinking at Zuka-chan-senpai's bar?
ずかちゃん先輩が
バイトしてる店で飲むんじゃ？
It's still too early for that.
まだ ちょっと早いよ
Then how about hitting Inokashira Park?
あっ じゃあ
井(い)の頭(かしら)公園行かない？
Why?
なんでですか？
The god of wealth is there!
弁財天がいるんだよ
（しずか）へえ～
（絵麻）知らなかった
I didn't know that!
That's one of the seven lucky divines!
七福神の聖地ですね
Matsu
Tei
Food and drinks
Cheers!
（一同）
かんぱ～い！
あ～ おいしい！
So good!
Here we are, drinking together...
お酒がおいしいって
思うようになるなんて
I guess we're all grown up now.
私たち大人になったよね
Here, on the house.
（店長）
はい これ　サービス
（一同）
わあ～
Thank you!
ありがとうございます
Thanks, boss!
すみません 店長
いや～ ずかちゃん
いつも頑張ってくれてるからさ
Zuka-chan's always working so hard!
You're my guest today,
so take your time and drink up!
今日は お客さんなんだから
ゆっくり飲んで
Thank you very much!
（しずか）
ありがとうございます
This place is really nice!
（あおい）
いいお店だね
Yeah, they are really nice to me.
（しずか）
うん すごく
よくしてもらってる
I watched Exodus!
あっ 「えくそだすっ！」
見ましたよ
同じく
Me too!
I went donuts when I saw your names in the credits,
Oi-chan-senpai, Ema-senpai!
おいちゃん先輩と絵麻先輩の
名前 見てジーンとしました
It's a dream come true that we all got jobs in the anime biz.
みんな本当にアニメの仕事に
就くなんて思いませんでしたね
Oi-chan-senpai's in production.
おいちゃん先輩が制作
絵麻先輩がアニメーター
Ema-senpai's an animator.
Zuka-chan-senpai's a voice actress.
ずかちゃん先輩が声優
More like wanna-be voice actress.
あ… 私はまだ卵だけどね
And I'm doing 3D!
それから私が３Ｄ
And I'm still a student.
私だけ まだ学生
But I'm definitely going to write an anime script!
でも絶対
アニメの脚本 書きます！
I'd love to write one, that is.
書きたいと思います
書けたらいいな…
I wish I could.
Don't give up yet, Rii-chan!
りーちゃんは これからだから
How's work lately?
最近どうですか？　仕事
あっ 私？
Me?
う～ん 絵を描くのは楽しいけど
仕事になると いろいろあるのよね
I enjoy drawing,
but when it's your job,
there's so much to worry about.
Like how I'm not good enough,
自分の下手さに落ち込んだり
時間のなさに あたふたしたり
and how I don't have enough time...
I know how that feels!
すごい分かります
私 先輩に叱られてばかりで
All the others keep yelling at me about how my work lacks detail
作り込みが甘いとか
and how I should pay more attention to scale and positioning.
もっとスケール感や
空間を意識してとか
I didn't think I was that bad.
もうちょっと自分はできると
思ってたんですけど
（あおい）うん 同じ同じ　私も
（美沙）あっ
Same here.
I totally panicked during episode 4.
４話の時なんかパニクっちゃって
My co-workers had to rush to my aid.
随分 周りの人に
助けてもらっちゃった
Sounds nice.
（しずか）いいな
（あおい）え？
Having little bumps in the road at work means you actually have real work already.
仕事のことで悩めるなんて
ちゃんと仕事してるってことだもん
I mean, I haven't done anything significant yet.
私なんて まだ
大したことやってないし
What do you mean?
（みどり）
大したこと？
Back home, I voiced the shopping mall mascot's...
地方の商店街のゆるキャラの…
A mascot? Those are so popular!
ゆるキャラ！
今 大人気じゃないですか
...rival's lackey, was it?
…のライバルの子分とか
Didn't you say you worked for a TV channel too?
あっ なんか
テレビの仕事したって
あっ バラエティーの
ボイスオーバーをちょっと
I did voice-over for a variety show.
Voice-over? What's that?
ボイスオーバー？
なんですか それ？
It's a show about international incidents,
so the voices are dubbed over to Japanese.
外国で起きた事件の
再現ドラマのね
外国の人に
声を当てるんだけど
What's it called?
なんの番組ですか？
Mysterious Happenings Around The World.
「不思議！　世界の珍事件」
っていう…
Wow, I know that one! Awesome!
あ～ 知ってる！
すごいじゃないですか
What voice was it?
ちなみに どんな声を？
Do it for us!
やってみてくださいよ
A dang UFO or whatever ya'll call it landed on our farm the other day.
最近 うちの農場に
ＵＦＯっつうのが来てよ
It surprised the heck outta me!
あたしゃビックラ
こいちまっただよ
Wow!
（絵麻）すごい
（みどり）うまい
Amazing!
That was a perfect old country woman!
今 ホントに田舎の
おばあちゃんの声だったよね
Like you stole her voice!
今 映像 見えたよ
But no one knows that was me.
でも誰も私がやってるって
気付かない仕事だし
（美沙）
あっ 昨日オーディション
受けたって聞きましたよ
I heard you had an audition yesterday.
Yeah.
I made a real mess of the audition, pretty much.
いや～ あたしゃ
失敗こいちまってさ～
I was so nervous, I couldn't hold the script steady!
緊張して原稿 持つ手が
震えちまって
Then at the most important part, my voice cracked.
肝心なところで
声は裏返っちゃうしさ
もうさんざん
It was awful.
And Souma Rena-san was
auditioning for the same part.
それに同じ役
相馬れなさんも受けてて
From Sadoka Mazoka?
「サドカマゾカ」の？
And Mon Mon Biyori and Aipuri?
「もんもんびより」や
「アイ･プリ」の？
She's tops for those older character roles!
年上系っていえば
今 相馬さんっすよね
So I probably stand no chance!
だから多分
私なんか無理無理！
Things don't always go smoothly in real life.
まあ現実は
そう甘くないよね！
I practiced thousands of times at home,
家で何千回も
練習したんだけどな
but when it mattered most, things still didn't go right.
本番では なかなか
うまくいかないもんだね　ハハハ…
There's always a next time!
次 頑張ろうよ
No one gets a leading role on her first try!
最初から
うまくいく人なんていないよ
This is just the beginning!
これからっす！
（美沙）うん りーちゃんもね
（みどり）うっす
That goes for you too!
Yeah!
Let's drink up, then!
よっし 飲も 飲も
おかわりする人～
Seconds, anyone?
I'll have another beer!
（しずか）
私 もう１杯ビール
Lemon sour for me!
私 レモンサワー
Cassis orange, I guess.
カシスオレンジにしようかな
And me...
（みどり）私は…
（携帯電話のバイブ音）
Musashino Animation
Incoming Call
Matsu
Tei
Food and drinks
Hello, Miyamori speaking.
はい 宮森です
Ah, Miyamori?
（太郎）
あ～ みゃーもり？
Oh, it's you, Takanashi-san.
なんだ高梨(たかなし)さんか
What was that?! I'm in neck deep!
（太郎）
なんだとはなんだ！
今 大変なんだよ俺は
Why would you call me on my day off?
なんですか 休みの日に
I thought you might be free.
（太郎）
いや～ お前が
一番 暇そうだからさ
If you don't need anything, I'm hanging up.
あの 用がないんだったら
切りますよ
（太郎）
あ～ ちょっと待って！
Wait a moment!
I do need something, actually.
用があるから電話してんだよ！
That said, it's not such a huge deal,
まあ そんなに
大したことじゃないんだけどさ
or maybe it is, kinda.
いや 少し大してるっていうか
Can it wait? I'm with my friends.
後でいいですか？
今 友達と会ってるんで
Oh yeah!
（太郎）
お～ そうだった！
かわいい子だらけの飲み会！
Send me a pic of the all-cutie party!
写メ送ってよ～
Excuse me.
（あおい）とりあえず失礼します
（太郎）ちょ ちょっと…
Wait a mo—
I'm so hyped for Fight this season.
私 今期は「ファイト」が
一押しなんですよ
The setting sounds amazing.
設定 深いっすよね～
The animation is great too.
（絵麻）作画もすごいし
（扉が開く音）
Sorry, I'm back!
（あおい）
ごめん ごめん
Here's your beer!
おいちゃんのビール来てるよ
Let's say cheers again! Cheers!
じゃあ もう一度 乾杯しよう
乾杯！
Ready, and... cheers!
（絵麻）
せ～の
Ready, and... cheers!
（一同）
かんぱ～い！
ふう～ うう～ん ああ～ん
（しずか）いい～ん
（店長）うん？
What's that, Zuka-chan?
ずかちゃん 何？
I think I got those right, at least.
これはね うまくできたと思うんだ
It must have to do with her audition.
オーディションの話じゃ
ないですか？
I'll keep trying hard!
I'd love to play a bunch of different roles.
次は私 頑張る
いろんな役ができたらいいな
I'm sure you'll be fine!
うん ずかちゃんなら大丈夫！
I wanna make people move in 3D!
私は３Ｄでキャラを動かしたい
Good luck!
うん 頑張って
I'd love to draw delicate animation like Horiuchi-san from Naniwa Animation.
私は なにわアニメーションの
堀内(ほりうち)さんみたいに
繊細な芝居が
描けるようになりたい
I see! You can do it!
そっか 絵麻なら大丈夫だよ
I wanna write the story for a fantasy epic like Big Saga!
私は「ビッグサーガ」みたいな
壮大なファンタジーものの
シナリオが書きたいです
If anyone could, it's you!
うん りーちゃんなら書ける！
And I—
私は！　うっ
（美沙）
あっ プロデューサーじゃ
ないですか？
Producer, isn't it?
A-girl Suzuki Toshizou!
よっ！　女 鈴木(すずき)敏造(としぞう)
Then make a feature movie out of The Divines!
そしたら七福陣の劇場版
作って作って～
Totally! I'll bump it up to a thousand lucky gods!
分かった 千福陣くらいに
パワーアップするよ！
So many characters to design...
キャラデ大変
Then let me do about three hundred of them!
（しずか）
じゃあ私300人くらい
兼役やらして～
Sure!
（あおい）
いいよ
Take care of Zuka-chan, please!
（あおい）
じゃあ ずかちゃん お願いね
Got it! I'll get her home, safe and sound!
はい ちゃんと
送り届けますんで
I'm also going to crash at her place.
そのまま泊めてもらいます
Sorry...
（あおい）
ごめんね
You all got work, after all.
いえ 皆さん お仕事ですから
We're doing a party for New Year's next! Yeah!
次は忘年会やろ 忘年会
Let's get going, Zuka-senpai.
さっ 帰りますよ ずか先輩
I didn't think Zuka-chan would get that tipsy.
ずかちゃんが あんなに
酔っ払うとは思わなかったね
It must be tough for voice actors too.
大変だね 声優になるのも
Yeah, but...
うん でも
私は ずかちゃんや
I got a bit jealous of you, Zuka-chan, and Mii-chan.
絵麻や みーちゃんのことも
ちょっといいなと思っちゃった
I don't have a clear goal in mind like you all do.
私は まだ具体的に
なんになりたいとか
何がしたいとか目標がなくて
What can I do?
私には何ができるのかな
I need to head to the supermarket and pick up lunch for tomorrow.
私 スーパー寄ってくね
あしたのお弁当 買ってく
They should be half price right now.
半額になってると思うから
Roger! See you!
了解～！　じゃあね
Bye!
バイバ～イ
Skip
Street
On the highest peaks of the Andes
Skip
Street
（“山はりねずみ
アンデスチャッキー”を歌う）
Skip
Street
there lived a cool mountain hedgeho—
What is it now?
なんすか～ 何回も
Are you drunk?
（太郎）
お前さ 酔っ払ってんの？
I'm fine! Don't worry!
大丈夫で～す
No one's worried about you!
（太郎）
お前の心配なんかしてねえよ
Geez! I'm having a really hard time right now!
まったくさ　俺がこんなに
大変な思いしてんのにさ
I don't like girls who drink, by the way.
あっ ちなみに
俺 酔っ払う女はＮＧ
Then find a wonderful girlfriend who doesn't drink and have her help you!
（あおい）
じゃあ 酔っ払わない
ステキな彼女 見つけて
助けてもらってくださ～い
Wait! I'm actually in over my head here! Don't hang—
（太郎）
あ～ 待って 待って…
マジピンチだから助けて！
切らないで…
On the highest peaks of the Andes
there lived a cool mountain hedgehog.
Andes Chucky...
You promised you'd finish the
storyboards by this week, right?
絵コンテ 週明けには上がるって
言いましたよね！
うん 言った
I did.
Then follow through on what you said!
言ったら守ってくださいよ
Then I'm un-saying it now.
じゃあ もう言わない
What are you, 12?!
子供ですか あなたは！
You can't make anime unless you're a kid at heart!
子供の心がないと
アニメは作れない！
う～ん 今日 組んだ作打ち
どうするんですか？
What do we do about the animator briefings today?
But...
（木下）だって…
（本田）だってじゃないです！
Don't "but" me!
The voice actors' scripts won't be done on time now!
このままじゃアフレコ台本
間に合いませんよ
At least show me how far you got.
う～ん せめて
どこまで出来たか見せてください
Wait! This is an invasion of privacy!
ギクッ あっ ちょっ… ちょっと
プライバシー侵害！　あっ
うん？　うん？　これ～
頭のとこしかないですけど
This is only the beginning of it.
Where's the rest?
続きはどこですか？
I'm sorry.
（木下）それだけ
（本田）37カットしかないですよ！
I only did thirty-seven cuts so far!
I'm sorry! I really am!
（木下）
すいません ホントすいません！
The room was so hot I couldn't concentrate!
いや～ 部屋が暑くて
集中できないんだよねっ
It's not the time for excuses like that, is it?
…っていう言い訳してる
場合じゃないよね
Then let's cool it down in here.
じゃあ とことん
寒くしてあげますよ
I wanna be able to see my breath! Go below freezing!
ガンガン下げてください
マイナスまでいきましょう！
Now tell me the truth.
でっ 隠し事なく
本当のこと教えてください
When exactly can you finish it?
正確に
いつ 上げていただけますか？
（木下）えっと あっ えっと…
（太郎）あの 遠藤(えんどう)さん―
Endou-san, please listen to me!
少しだけ僕の話を聞いてください
I'm done listening to you!
（遠藤）
もう お前と話すことはない
Endou-san, let's have fun working together!
（太郎）
遠藤さん あの もっと
楽しく仕事しましょうよ
Don't be such a wuss. You're not a child.
Endou Ryousuke
Animation Director
いいかげん
機嫌 直してくださいよ
遠藤さんも大人げないな～
Shimoyanagi's the one acting like a child here!
大人げないのは下柳(しもやなぎ)のほうだろ
If you say so. If you need a punching bag,
you know where to find me.
ですよね　僕でよければ
いくらでもサンドバッグになります
Shut up!
（遠藤）うるさい！
（太郎）いっ
I've had enough!
（遠藤）
もう我慢の限界だ
俺は８話の作監 降りるからな！
Find another AD for episode 8!
This is Musashino Animation.
What? Takanashi did?
Hey, Tarou!
Next time on Shirobako:
"If You're Gonna Blame Others for Everything, Just Quit!"
If You're Gonna Blame Others for Everything, Just Quit!
（矢野）
はい 武蔵野(むさしの)アニメーションです
えっ 高梨が？
ちょっと 太郎！
次回「SHIROBAKO(シロバコ)」